adprudence.com 2012-06-24

# Privacy « « AdPrudence

**Acceptance of Terms**

Please read this policy carefully since by visiting this website (Website) and/or sharing information with us, you agree to be bound by this Privacy Policy. The Privacy Policy may be revised or updated at any time by us. This page was last updated as of 23rd Oct, 2011. 

**Summary**

We do not collect personally identifiable information (data collected with an intention to identify and contact a person such as name, address, telephone number or e-mail address) (hereinafter �PII�). The non-personally identifiable information we collect may include as an example, IP address, browser types, operating systems, domain names, access dates and times, referring website addresses, online transactions and browsing and search activity. We may use your Non-PII (�Information�) for the following general purposes: enhancement of our services, marketing, and to more effectively match advertisements and website content to your interests. We may share your Information with third party service providers we have contracted with. You may regulate the collection of your Information through your browser settings or use of �opt-out Cookies�. We use reasonable and appropriate security measures to protect your data. We may change the Privacy Policy at any time by posting the revised Privacy Policy on the Website and if such changes are material, a notice of the changes will also be posted along with the revised Privacy Policy. Members of the AdPrudence Network include publishers and advertisers involved in advertising campaign transactions. Member information collected includes personally identifiable information that is necessary to conduct business, such as name, phone number, and email address. Payments made to and from AdPrudence require the collection of personally identifiable information that may include credit card numbers and bank account information. Phone numbers may be used to contact Members for sales or inventory acquisition purposes. All Member information is collected, modified and stored in a password protected environment. This information is used for service, media delivery, contact, billing and accounts payable purposes. We will not sell, share, or rent this information to non-AdPrudence entities. All Member information collection is explicit, voluntary, manually entered by the Member. If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, the practices of or your dealings with us relating to this Privacy Policy, please email us: contactus@adprudence.com. 

**Opt-Out**

We may use third-party advertising companies as a backfill to serve ads when it is necessary. These companies may use information (not including your name, address email address or telephone number) about your visits in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, click here: (http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp). 

**Security**

AdPrudence employs appropriate measures to ensure the security of all Information and We routinely evaluate our practices to identify security threats or opportunities for the improvement of our services. No transmission of information is guaranteed to be completely secure. Unauthorized entry or use, hardware or software failure, and other factors may compromise data security. You acknowledge and agree to assume this risk when communicating with us. 

**Changes**

As the standards governing Internet privacy continue to evolve, AdPrudence may find it appropriate or necessary to update this Privacy Policy from time to time. As a result, we reserve the right to change this privacy policy at any time and shall post such changes on the Website. Our Website will state the date the Privacy Policy was last updated. We encourage you to review the Privacy Policy whenever you use this Website to make sure you understand how your information will be used. 

**Your Representations**

YOU UNDERSTAND AND AGREE THAT ANY DISPUTE OVER PRIVACY IS SUBJECT TO THE TERMS AND CONDITIONS OF THIS PRIVACY POLICY AND APPLICABLE SITE TERMS AND CONDITIONS. You also agree that you have provided notice to, and obtained consent from, any third party individuals whose Information you supply to us with regard to: (a) the purposes for which such third party's Information has been collected; (b) the intended recipients or categories of recipients of the third party's Information; � which of the third party's data are obligatory and which data, if any, are voluntary; and (d) how the third party can access and, if necessary, rectify the data held about them. It is the express wish of the parties that the Privacy Policy and all related documents have been drawn up in the English language.
